<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>UMass Amherst CS Women</title>
    <description>Promoting the representation and interests of women in computing. </description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 10:08:37 -0400</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 10:08:37 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.8.5</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Su Lin Blodgett describes her research and what makes CICS a great place for women graduate students</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Su Lin Blodgett, PhD student at UMass, describes her research and what makes CICS a great place for women graduate students.
&lt;br /&gt;
Click below to watch her video.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wZMX8mb1ln8&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/su-youtube_video.PNG&quot; alt=&quot;Su Lin's experience&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Mar 2018 20:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/su-lin-blodgett/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/su-lin-blodgett/</guid>
        
        
        <category>social</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rumeng Li attends AMIA 2017 Annual Symposium at Washington, D.C.</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;In early November, I went to attend AMIA (American Medical Informatics Association) 2017 Annual Symposium at Washington D.C. The conference is about informatics for improving health and making better healthcare decisions, basically in five domains of informatics: translational bioinformatics, clinical research informatics, clinical informatics, consumer health informatics, and public health informatics. I went to present my paper of using natural language processing method for data mining in Electronic Health Records. I am very happy that people showed interest on my work and asked me questions, and I also got valuable insights from them for future work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/blog/travel-li-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Li-conference&quot; style=&quot;margin: 15px 10px 10px 0; height=500px; width=600px&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Besides the keynote presentations, various talks, poster sessions and workshops, AMIA also offers rich networking opportunities, like AMIA New Member and First Time Attendee Reception, Women in AMIA Networking Event, AMIA dancing party etc. It’s great to talk with researchers working in different aspects of medical informatics and to learn from them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/blog/travel-li-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Li-poster&quot; style=&quot;margin: 15px 10px 10px 0; height=600px; width=400px&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In general, it’s a wonderful and very rewarding experience for me. I am very thankful to &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.umass.edu/wfum/&quot;&gt;Women for UMass Amherst&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://cswomenumass.github.io/index.html&quot;&gt;CSWomen group&lt;/a&gt; for providing the generous financial support, which help covered part of the travel expenses.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2017 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/travel-li/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/travel-li/</guid>
        
        
        <category>travelgrant</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tiffany Liu attends summer school program on Cognitive Architectures at CITEC, Germany</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;As my summer of 2017 came to a close, I had the fortune of attending a &lt;a href=&quot;https://cit-ec.de/en/graduate-school/summerschool&quot;&gt;week-long summer school program on Cognitive Architectures&lt;/a&gt; at Universität Bielefeld Cluster of Excellence Cognitive Interaction Technology (&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cit-ec.de/en&quot;&gt;CITEC&lt;/a&gt;) in Germany.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/blog/travel-liu-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Liu-Cognitive Architecture Banner&quot; style=&quot;margin: 15px 10px 10px 0; height=600px; width=600px&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Days were filled with keynote talks on cognitive architectures geared towards applications in robotics from senior researchers who are well-known in their research areas. In the afternoon, we split into subgroups where each group was assigned a robotic platform and a task to complete by the end of the week. I was assigned to Pepper, a humanoid robot from SoftBank Robotics, with the task of having it learn how to play the cup-and-ball game. While the task was rather disconnected from the cognitive architecture theme we saw during the keynote talks, it was still fun and interesting to work with a different robotic platform than what I normally use in my lab.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/blog/travel-liu-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Liu - Pepper robot&quot; style=&quot;margin: 15px 10px 10px 0; height=600px; width=600px&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The best part of this whole experience was the unique networking opportunity. CITEC Summer School drew in around 30 young researchers from not only robotics, but also psychology, biology, linguistics, and other subfields of computer science. The majority of the participants were from European research institutions (I was the only from the U.S.). As such I was able to discuss my research interest and bounce ideas off of people both inside and outside the robotics community as well as promote the ongoing work of the robotics community at UMass Amherst. The relatively small and diverse attendance was definitely unique to the summer school and something you would not normally get to experience from larger, more field-targeted conferences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you so much &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.umass.edu/wfum/&quot;&gt;Women for UMass Amherst&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://cswomenumass.github.io/index.html&quot;&gt;CS Women&lt;/a&gt; for providing the financial support to subsidize a portion of this trip!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/blog/travel-liu-3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Liu's experience&quot; style=&quot;margin: 15px 10px 10px 0; height=600px; width=600px&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 20:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/travel-liu/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/travel-liu/</guid>
        
        
        <category>travelgrant</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>SouYoung attends CVPR 2017 at Hawaii</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/wfum_logo.png&quot; alt=&quot;WFUM logo&quot; /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Thanks to the support of &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.umass.edu/wfum/&quot;&gt;Women for UMass Amherst&lt;/a&gt;, we have awarded another &lt;a href=&quot;http://cswomenumass.github.io/travelgrant.html&quot;&gt;Travel Grant&lt;/a&gt;! Sou Young received $500 to cover the costs of her visit to &lt;a href=&quot;http://cvpr2017.thecvf.com/&quot;&gt;IEEE’s computer vision and pattern recognition conference&lt;/a&gt;. Below is her impression of the event.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Hawaii is a really great place for summer vacation, but I have experienced something different this summer by attending a conference there! It is IEEE/CVF computer vision and pattern recognition (CVPR) which is one of the top-tier conferences in the computer vision community. Thanks to CS Women, I could attend this year’s CVPR and present my workshop paper at &lt;a href=&quot;https://sites.google.com/view/fgvc4/home&quot;&gt;Fine-Grained Visual Categorization (FGVC)&lt;/a&gt;. My work is to group faces in a movie without any supervision, which can cluster the same person with a unique ID. In the poster session, I introduced my proposed work and showed a demo video. I discussed my work with many people and got a lot of valuable comments. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/blog/travel-jin-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;SouYoung at her poster presentation&quot; /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
During the main conference, as there are enormous amount of papers, I had to use my time efficiently. So, everyday I woke up in the morning, I went through all the papers in the list and read some abstracts to check which oral/poster presentations I would like to visit. Then, I read the papers more deeply or visited the corresponding posters to talk with authors at the spot, which is the best part of attending a conference!! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
This CVPR had around 200 sponsors from industry, and there were many interesting exhibition booths. Here is a photo of me enjoying the real-time style-transfer demo from NVIDIA. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/blog/travel-jin-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;SouYoung at Nvidia's style-transfer demo&quot; /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
In addition to the exhibitions, some companies also held interesting after-dinner events, and I could have good discussions on my research with people who are currently working on the companies. In this CVPR, I have learned a lot and had invaluable experience in my life. I really appreciate of UMass CS Women’s help in giving me the financial support for the conference registration! :) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/blog/travel-jin-3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Hawaii, USA&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2017 20:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/travel-jin/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/travel-jin/</guid>
        
        
        <category>travelgrant</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sandhya Subramanian presents her paper at ICAPS 2017, held at CMU</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;In past years, CSWomen has held lunch series, technical workshops, mentoring programs and provided travel grants to help women of CICS UMass Amherst, present themselves at various global fronts. Sandhya Subramanian has written a wonderful essay on her experiences at ICAPS this year, which we have reproduced in detail below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In June 2017, I had the opportunity to present my paper at the International Conference on Automated Planning and Scheduling (ICAPS) 2017. The paper titled “Optimizing Electric Vehicle Charging Through Determinization” was a joint work with Prof. Shlomo Zilberstein and Prof. Prashant Shenoy, and was based on my synthesis project. The conference was held in Carnegie Mellon University. Thanks to the support of CS Women travel grant, I was able to travel to Pittsburgh, PA to present my paper.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The conference, including the workshops, was a 5-day event and the attendees were a mix of students, professors, and researchers from the industry. It turned out to be a wonderful experience for me to meet my research community from around the world and share ideas. I was also able to attend several talks and workshop sessions that were part of the conference. It was interesting to hear from many different perspectives and I was able to learn a lot from the speakers at the sessions of workshop and the conference, and from conversations with the other attendees.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Almost everyday, there were panel discussions towards the end of the day. The topics for the panel discussion were very interesting and were centered around the various perspectives of future research directions in AI Planning. The panelists were a mix of renowned professors, sharing their views from different an academia perspective, and researchers from the industry, sharing their views from an industry perspective. Here’s a picture of the panel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/blog/travel-subramanian-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Sandhya's Experience 1&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The coffee breaks were ideal for casual discussions among the attendees. My interaction with few professors and fellow PhD students during the coffee breaks helped me gain some valuable insights regarding future directions of my current research. Their feedback was very useful and their enthusiasm for my work increased my confidence!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall, the event was enjoyable and beneficial to me. I am thankful to Women for UMass Amherst and CSWomen group for providing their generous financial support. It helped cover some of the travel expenses to attend this wonderful event!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2017 20:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/travel-subramanian/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/travel-subramanian/</guid>
        
        
        <category>travelgrant</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Amanda Doucette Travels to the Cognitive Modeling and Computational Linguistics workshop at EACL 2017</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/wfum_logo.png&quot; alt=&quot;WFUM logo&quot; style=&quot;float: left; margin:0 15px 10px 0; width: 300px; &quot; /&gt;
Thanks to the support of &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.umass.edu/wfum/&quot;&gt;Women for UMass Amherst&lt;/a&gt;, we have awarded another &lt;a href=&quot;http://cswomenumass.github.io/travelgrant.html&quot;&gt;Travel Grant&lt;/a&gt;! Amanda Doucette received $500 to cover the costs of her visit to the &lt;a href=&quot;http://cmcl2017.osu.edu/&quot;&gt;Cognitive Modeling and Computational Linguistics workshop&lt;/a&gt;. Below is her impression of the event.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;As someone who has never been to a research conference before, let alone presented a poster at one, I was excited to attend the &lt;a href=&quot;http://cmcl2017.osu.edu/&quot;&gt;Cognitive Modeling and Computational Linguistics workshop&lt;/a&gt; at &lt;a href=&quot;http://eacl2017.org/&quot;&gt;EACL 2017&lt;/a&gt; with the support of the &lt;a href=&quot;http://cswomenumass.github.io/travelgrant.html&quot;&gt;CSWomen Travel Grant&lt;/a&gt;. Without it, I wouldn’t have been able to travel to Valencia, Spain to present my undergraduate thesis research.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Having never attended a research conference before, I didn’t know what to expect at the conference. I was there to present my undergraduate thesis, “Inherent Biases of Recurrent Neural Networks for Phonological Assimilation and Dissimilation”, which I have been working on with &lt;a href=&quot;http://blogs.umass.edu/pater/&quot;&gt;Joe Pater&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://brenocon.com/&quot;&gt;Brendan O’Connor&lt;/a&gt; for the past year. I presented my research at the workshop’s poster session, but I also was able to attend several talks that were a part of the workshop earlier in the day.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
While most of my research has been in computational phonology, it was exciting to hear from researchers in other areas of cognitive modeling and computational linguistics. The attendees of the workshop were a mix of students, professors, and researchers in both computer science and linguistics, so it was interesting to hear from many different perspectives. I felt like I was able to learn a lot from the speakers at the workshop and from conversations with the other people there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Towards the end of the day, I presented my poster at a poster session that was combined with several other EACL workshops. Because of this, I was able to talk to people with a background in NLP research, rather than in cognitive modeling and linguistics, and was able to have some really useful conversations about my research. It was exciting to be able to finally tell people about what I’ve been working on for the past year, and I’m really glad I was able to meet everyone I talked to at the workshop.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
I never thought it would be possible for me to present my research at a conference in Spain as an undergraduate student, but thanks to &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.umass.edu/wfum/&quot;&gt;Women for UMass Amherst&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://cswomenumass.github.io/index.html&quot;&gt;CSWomen group&lt;/a&gt;, I was able to. The workshop was a really great experience for me, as was spending a few days in Spain!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/travelgrant/amanda_travelgrant1.png&quot; alt=&quot;Valencia, Spain&quot; style=&quot;margin: 15px 10px 10px 0; ; width=600px&quot; /&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;/images/travelgrant/amanda_travelgrant2.png&quot; alt=&quot;Valencia, Spain&quot; style=&quot;margin: 15px 10px 10px 0; ; width=600px&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2017 20:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/travel-doucette/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/travel-doucette/</guid>
        
        
        <category>travelgrant</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>CSWomen Social: Paint Night</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;CSWomen paint night was a big success thanks to the great work of our Social Committee! We also thank our photographer for providing pictures of the event. For more pictures visit our &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/groups/cswomen.umass/permalink/1843534889247839/&quot;&gt;Facebook page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/blog/social-paint-night-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Paint Night 1&quot; style=&quot;margin:15px 10px 10px 0; width=700px&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/blog/social-paint-night-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Paint Night 2&quot; style=&quot;margin:15px 10px 10px 0; width=700px&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/blog/social-paint-night-3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Paint Night 3&quot; style=&quot;margin:15px 10px 10px 0; width=700px&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2017 20:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/social-paint-night/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/social-paint-night/</guid>
        
        
        <category>social</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rachee Singh Travels to Google Networking Research Summit</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/wfum_logo.png&quot; alt=&quot;WFUM logo&quot; style=&quot;float: left; margin:0 15px 10px 0; width: 300px; &quot; /&gt;
Thanks to the support of &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.umass.edu/wfum/&quot;&gt;Women for UMass Amherst&lt;/a&gt;, we have awarded out first &lt;a href=&quot;http://cswomenumass.github.io/travelgrant.html&quot;&gt;Travel Grant&lt;/a&gt;! Rachee Singh received $500 to cover the costs of her visit to Google Networking Research Summit. Below is her impression of the event.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;This February, Google organized a Networking Research Summit to engage with academics performing research in various areas of computer networking. My PhD advisor, Dr. Phillipa Gill, was invited to attend the summit to present recent work from our lab, &lt;a href=&quot;http://calipr.cs.umass.edu/&quot;&gt;Calipr&lt;/a&gt; at UMass Amherst. Google also invited a few PhD students and on my advisor’s nomination I received an invite to attend the Networking Research Summit at Google Mountain View!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
The summit was a congregation of very well known and accomplished networking researchers. The discussion began with an outline of milestones in the development of Google’s networking infrastructure and the open challenges that they face. This spurred an engaging discussion where academics asked questions and gave ideas to solve the open problems. This style of understanding the practical problems and proposing solutions was the overall theme of the entire summit.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
In the next two days, the essence of the bleeding edge of networking research was presented to an audience comprising of students, professors and Googlers through a series of talks and panel discussions. Talks by Google engineers and scientists were interspersed among talks by professors from various universities in the world.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
The coffee breaks offered a great opportunity to meet Googlers who gave us a peek into the kind of problems they work on. I found this perspective unique and thought provoking. Also, being fairly new to the networking research community, I got the chance to interact with many PhD students from other institutions. Google had also organized a poster session for PhD students. I presented our work on PathCache, a network path prediction toolkit. People had great suggestions and feedback for us that we are actively working on.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
The event was enjoyable and beneficial to me and I hope Google continues to organize it. I am also thankful to &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.umass.edu/wfum/&quot;&gt;Women for UMass Amherst&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://cswomenumass.github.io/index.html&quot;&gt;CSWomen group&lt;/a&gt; for providing their generous financial support. It helped cover some of the travel expenses to attend this wonderful event!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/blog/travel-singh-1.png&quot; alt=&quot;Google Summit&quot; style=&quot;margin: 15px 10px 10px 0; width=750px&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 20:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/travel-singh/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/travel-singh/</guid>
        
        
        <category>travelgrant</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>CSWomen Social: High Horse</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The first social event of the semester, a casual gathering at High Horse for food and drinks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/blog/social_high_horse_1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;High Horse 1&quot; style=&quot;margin:15px 10px 10px 0; width=700px&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/blog/social_high_horse_2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;High Horse 2&quot; style=&quot;margin:15px 10px 10px 0; width=700px&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/blog/social_high_horse_3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;High Horse 3&quot; style=&quot;margin:15px 10px 10px 0; width=700px&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2017 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/social-high-horse/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/social-high-horse/</guid>
        
        
        <category>social</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>First Lunch of 2017</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The first lunch meeting of Spring 2017 happened on Wednesday, February 1. We presented &lt;a href=&quot;http://cswomenumass.github.io/travelgrant.html&quot;&gt;CSWomen Travel Grant program&lt;/a&gt; and introduced new officers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--break--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Graduate co-chair&lt;/strong&gt;: Nidhi Mundra&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;MS co-chair&lt;/strong&gt;: Eva Moscovici&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Social committee&lt;/strong&gt;: Katherine Keith, Amee Trivedi, and Roopa Shenoy&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2017 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/lunch/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/lunch/</guid>
        
        
        <category>lunch</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
