<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-02-12T21:33:24-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">UMass Amherst CS Women</title><subtitle>Promoting the representation and interests of women in computing. </subtitle><entry><title type="html">GHC Information Panel - Summary</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/lunch-ghc20/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="GHC Information Panel - Summary" /><published>2020-02-10T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2020-02-10T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/lunch-ghc20</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/lunch-ghc20/">&lt;p&gt;CSWomen conducted its first lunch event of the spring semester on Feb 12, 2020; an information session on conferences focused on diversity in technology. Here is a summary of the discussion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;different-conferences-for-inclusion-and-diversity&quot;&gt;Different conferences for inclusion and diversity:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://ghc.anitab.org/2020-attend/&quot;&gt;Grace Hopper Celebration (Sept 29 - Oct 2)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;: It is a celebration of women in computing, and boasts of over 25000 attendees every year. Key events include the career fair, poster presentations, panels, workshops, and talks. CICS awards grants for attending the conference. See below for various additional scholarships opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Richard Tapia Celebration (Sept 16 - 19)&lt;/strong&gt;: It is a celebration of diversity in computing, with focus on under-represented ethnicities, disabilities and genders. CICS awards grants for attending the conference. Scholarships open &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://tapiaconference.org/participate/scholarships&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://cra.org/cra-wp/grad-cohort-for-women/&quot;&gt;Grad Cohort Workshop for Women (April 16-19)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;: A workshop with formal and informal presentations on navigating graduate life. This is usually geared towards PhD students, but Master’s students considering a PhD should also apply to attend (applications for this year are closed, and will open sometime in October/November for the next year).&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.widscentralmass.org/&quot;&gt;Central Massachusetts Women in Data Science (March 2)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;: A day-long technical conference on latest data science research and applications. (Registration is currently open and free!).&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;how-to-attend-ghc&quot;&gt;How to Attend GHC:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are various scholarships that can be availed to attend GHC.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://ghc.anitab.org/2020-student-academic/scholarships/&quot;&gt;GHC Scholars Program&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;: The official AnitaB.org scholarship. This requires submitting an application with a couple of essay questions on why you want to attend GHC and how will you give back. A faculty recommendation is also required.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://ghc.anitab.org/2020-attend/woc-registration/&quot;&gt;GHC Women of Color in Technology Complimentary Registration&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://ghc.anitab.org/2020-speakers/session-formats-requirements&quot;&gt;ACM Student Research Competition&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;: You can submit your individual past/ongoing research project abstract. If accepted to speak at the poster session, ACM will cover upto $500 for travel/registration/accomodation. Interesting work done for your class projects can count!&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://ghc.anitab.org/hoppers/&quot;&gt;Hopper’s Program&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;: You can volunteer for 5-8 hours spread over 3 days at the conference, and receive complimentary registration in return.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/Ladies-Storm-Hackathons/GHC-Scholarships&quot;&gt;Industry scholarships&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;: Several companies like Google, Twitter, Facebook, etc. sponsor a few students each year to attend GHC. The link above keeps track of all such opportunities and is frequently updated. The information is crowd-sourced, so if you hear of an opportunity, please submit a pull request!&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;CICS travel grant for GHC: CICS sponsors 8-10 women from the department every year. The focus is more on undergrad women, but some Master’s students are also awarded the grant. Please note that CSWomen monthly travel grant does not cover GHC.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you do not receive a scholarship, you can buy a registration ($450) from GHC. Make sure to keep track of the date and time of registration; tickets are usually sold out in a few minutes. Also follow AnitaB.org on social media for real time updates on registration issues if any.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are unable to secure a registration on the website, there are official AnitaB.org - moderated Facebook groups that you can join, where people who are unable to attend the conference can transfer their registration to you. Please be aware of scams, and do not buy overpriced registration tickets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please keep an eye on the deadlines!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;navigating-the-career-fair&quot;&gt;Navigating the career fair:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Submit your resume to the GHC resume database early (months before the conference starts!), so that the companies attending GHC can potentially reach out to you before and after the conference.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Make a list of the companies that you are really interested in, and talk to them on the first day.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Coordinate with your friends; talk to different companies and compare notes periodically!&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Take multiple copies of your resume.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Carry food and water with you.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Wear comfortable shoes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;general-advice&quot;&gt;General advice&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Take advantage of the fact that you are in a place with 25000 women in tech! While the career fair is a wonderful opportunity, do take the time to attend other sessions, and network with women from the field.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;As the conference is huge, it can be a little overwhelming in terms of what companies to talk to at the career fair, what sessions to attend, and how best to network. Accept the fact that you will not be able to cover everything and prioritize what you want to attend.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Networking can be challenging; it is okay to connect with fewer people and focus on quality.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Companies often conduct social/networking events at the conference. Do attend these if invited; it can be very interesting to talk to employees. Keep on top of your email for such invitations!&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;If attending without a scholarship, get shared accommodation with friends, or find other attendees through Facebook groups.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;As the conference gets nearer, install the GHC app to register for sessions, see the map of the career fair, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Enjoy what Orlando has to offer! Most scholarships mentioned above give you the option to extend your stay by a day (accomodation not covered), so take the time to explore the place!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;experience-highlights&quot;&gt;Experience highlights&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Pracheta: To witness the energy of 25000 women in computing was definitely a great memory. I enjoyed listening to the overview and highlights of the different avenues that everyone is pursuing and being able to interact and network with them was enriching.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Akshita: I was invited to attend DeepMind’s panel on various topics ranging from the potential of AI, to healthy company culture. It was wonderful to discuss these things with employees from DeepMind, and to hear diverse ideas from other student attendees!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Shyla: GHC 2019 gave me an opportunity to meet and connect with some of the most inspiring women working in tech. The highlight of my experience was meeting Dr. Fei Fei Li who has always been a great source of inspiration for me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you all for attending the information session! Please let us know if you have any questions.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>linglonglinglong</name></author><summary type="html">CSWomen conducted its first lunch event of the spring semester on Feb 12, 2020; an information session on conferences focused on diversity in technology. Here is a summary of the discussion.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/blog/ghc-20.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Elita Ferrando Attended NeurIPS 2019</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/travel-lobo/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Elita Ferrando Attended NeurIPS 2019" /><published>2020-02-03T19:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2020-02-03T19:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/travel-lobo</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/travel-lobo/">&lt;p&gt;I recently got the opportunity to attend The Neural Information Processing Systems (Neurips) Conference at Vancouver. Before I describe my experience, I would like to thank to CS Women and Women for UMass Amherst for supporting me with the travel grant without which attending this conference would have been difficult. 
Through this conference I met several RL researchers like Richard Sutton, Doina Precup, Mohammad Ghavamzadeh etc whose work I have been closely following so it was a dream come true when I finally got an opportunity to discuss my research work with some of them!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I gained invaluable knowledge from the workshops and tutorials. My favorite workshops were Safe Reinforcement Learning workshop and Deep Reinforcement Learning workshop and I am glad that through these workshops I was able to get feedback on my project ideas and also get a better understanding of the current research work directly from the top researchers in Deepmind and OpenAI. I particularly liked the talk on Batch Reinforcement Learning by Emma Brunskill. We also had a fun social dinner where we got to interact with several professors and got useful advice from them on how to find and answer important questions while doing research. Additionally, I met several researchers from top companies and discussed potential internship opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also realized the necessity of being aware of research done in fields other than your own research field for making good progress in your research.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I returned from the conference feeling enlightened with so much knowledge and a better understanding of my own field of research.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In all, I had an great time at the conference and it was a great place to meet fellow researchers and discuss interesting ideas. I look forward to attending many more such conferences in near future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am glad that our university has a great CSWomen group that encourages women in CS to participate in such programs and I hope some days I would be able to be a part of the group and do the same.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>linglonglinglong</name></author><summary type="html">I recently got the opportunity to attend The Neural Information Processing Systems (Neurips) Conference at Vancouver. Before I describe my experience, I would like to thank to CS Women and Women for UMass Amherst for supporting me with the travel grant without which attending this conference would have been difficult. Through this conference I met several RL researchers like Richard Sutton, Doina Precup, Mohammad Ghavamzadeh etc whose work I have been closely following so it was a dream come true when I finally got an opportunity to discuss my research work with some of them!</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Cecilia Ferrando Attended NeurIPS 2019</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/travel-cecilia/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Cecilia Ferrando Attended NeurIPS 2019" /><published>2019-12-30T19:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2019-12-30T19:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/travel-cecilia</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/travel-cecilia/">&lt;p&gt;This December I attended my first NeurIPS conference, the largest conference in Machine Learning and AI. The 33rd edition has gathered 13,000 attendees, with a program covering all subfields of AI. The conference is so large that attendee tickets are assigned via a lottery. As a first-year PhD student, I entered the lottery with little hope, but to my surprise, I won a ticket and complimentary registration. Thanks to the CS Women Group travel funds, I have been able to catch this opportunity and attend the conference. My personal goal was to get to know NeurIPS and keep up-to-date about the main research directions in machine learning this year. Here are a few highlights from my week at NeurIPS 2019 in Vancouver, BC.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A few thematic lines emerged from the conference. The problem of the limitations of deep neural networks, and in particular, generalization, has been recurrent. As pointed out by Yoshua Bengio in his talk, out-of-distribution generalization is still a missing piece of the puzzle for deep learning to reach the status of human-level AI. From the current state of deep learning, we need to shift to a framework in which high-level representations and causal discovery are possible. Other limitations of the current state of Machine Learning are in its social implications. For example, privacy is becoming an increasing concern in today’s machine learning scene: on-device inference and federated learning are emerging as a way to train machine learning models on user data while keeping information decentralized (and private).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;NeurIPS is a great opportunity for in-depth exploration of specific research topics. In my case, I especially followed the privacy-related talks. Differential privacy (my current field of research) has gained momentum and I had the opportunity to connect with many researchers presenting their work in this field. This has been useful for me to inscribe my research work in a larger perspective. I got a sense of what directions differential privacy is taking and how it is being applied to various problems. NeurIPS can also be experienced as a breadth-wise expo of pretty much all machine learning research branches. I enjoyed exploring a variety of research topics that are not yet part of my work and wish to study in the future. Among these, causal inference, which is also gaining momentum, both in academic and industry research.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even with prior knowledge on its importance, NeurIPS still had a big wow effect on me the first day I arrived. 13,000 attendees, 1,428 accepted papers, 51 workshops. With so much going on, and so many people, I admit it has been an overwhelming experience at first. On day 1, I attended all morning sessions, tried to stop at every poster (that was of course impossible!), and sat at all afternoon sessions. By the end of the day, I felt overloaded with information and burned out. My advice for first-timers at NeurIPS is to tailor a personalized agenda, balancing your own field of research and other areas. Then let go of the frustration of missing out on all the rest – when I did, I started enjoying the conference way more! I really enjoyed the social aspects of NeurIPS: networking with other researchers from around the globe has been a fun experience, as well as attending company networking events. In particular, I had a great time at the Google Women in Research reception, where I had the chance to connect with fellow women researchers at different stages in their careers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Attending NeurIPS 2019 has been an enriching experience and I am looking forward to attending future editions. I wish to thank the CSWomen Travel Grant Committee for awarding me travel funding that has contributed to covering my trip expenses to the conference.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cecilia Ferrando&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>linglonglinglong</name></author><summary type="html">This December I attended my first NeurIPS conference, the largest conference in Machine Learning and AI. The 33rd edition has gathered 13,000 attendees, with a program covering all subfields of AI. The conference is so large that attendee tickets are assigned via a lottery. As a first-year PhD student, I entered the lottery with little hope, but to my surprise, I won a ticket and complimentary registration. Thanks to the CS Women Group travel funds, I have been able to catch this opportunity and attend the conference. My personal goal was to get to know NeurIPS and keep up-to-date about the main research directions in machine learning this year. Here are a few highlights from my week at NeurIPS 2019 in Vancouver, BC.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Aartika Rai Attended WiML 2019 in Vancouver, Canada</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/travel-aartika/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Aartika Rai Attended WiML 2019 in Vancouver, Canada" /><published>2019-12-25T19:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2019-12-25T19:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/travel-aartika</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/travel-aartika/">&lt;p&gt;Thanks to CS Women and Women for UMass, I attended the Women in Machine Learning workshop held in Vancouver, Canada, on December 9th. At the poster session, I presented my research work on ‘Learning 3D Priors with Adversarial Novel-View Generation’, a project I had been pursuing at UMass with professor Subhransu Maji and Matheus Gadelha. This was my first time attending an academic conference and presenting my work outside the university setting. Getting to discuss my ideas and results with a wider audience was very rewarding. The poster session was a great exercise in communicating my ideas with people from varying backgrounds. I’m grateful for all the encouraging feedback and insightful suggestions I received during the session.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Although the poster sessions were the main highlight of the event for me, WiML’s entire program was packed with learning opportunities. Thanks to mentorship roundtables, we got the chance to talk with brilliant scientists such as Yan LeCun and Hugo Larochelle. The tables featured a variety of topics from research to career at giants such as Apple and Google, to practical lessons on work-life balance and much more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall, it was a wonderful experience, and I’d encourage others to present their work at WiML. It’s a great way to meet accomplished researchers and get feedback on your ongoing projects.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>linglonglinglong</name></author><summary type="html">Thanks to CS Women and Women for UMass, I attended the Women in Machine Learning workshop held in Vancouver, Canada, on December 9th. At the poster session, I presented my research work on ‘Learning 3D Priors with Adversarial Novel-View Generation’, a project I had been pursuing at UMass with professor Subhransu Maji and Matheus Gadelha. This was my first time attending an academic conference and presenting my work outside the university setting. Getting to discuss my ideas and results with a wider audience was very rewarding. The poster session was a great exercise in communicating my ideas with people from varying backgrounds. I’m grateful for all the encouraging feedback and insightful suggestions I received during the session.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/blog/travel-aartika.jpeg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Fall 2019 Semester Recap</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/fall2019_semester_recap/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Fall 2019 Semester Recap" /><published>2019-12-22T19:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2019-12-22T19:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/fall2019_semester_recap</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/fall2019_semester_recap/">&lt;p&gt;Hi CSWomen,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our CSWomen group has had quite the exciting semester! First, I want to extend a big thank-you to all our officers who have put in a lot of time and effort to make our CSWomen events possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This semester, we organized community-building social events, partnered with other groups who brought prominent women in computer science to speak at UMass, and funded women to attend conferences with our travel grant. Here’s a recap of our activities this semester:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Speaker Events&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Hema Raghavan, Director of Engineering at LinkedIn (9/20)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Ayanna Howard, Mark C. Smith Professor and Chair of the School of Interactive Computing in the College of Computing at Georgia Tech (10/7)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Graduate Student Panel (12/3)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Career Events&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Google Resume Workshop (9/20)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Social Events&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Semester welcome and board games lunch (9/11)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Weekly Tuesday Teas&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Mt. Norwottuck Hike (10/4)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Halloween Tea (10/31)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Travel Grant&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Funded travel grants to 12 women in 2019 (9 for students presenting research papers, 1 to a summer school, and 2 special interest summits).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We hope you will continue to attend our events next semester to strengthen and grow our community of graduate women here at UMass!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Best, 
Katie&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/blog/halloween_tea.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;CSWomen Halloween tea.&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/blog/cswomen_hike.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;CSWomen hike to Mt. Norwotuck.&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>katie</name></author><summary type="html">Hi CSWomen,</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/blog/whole_group.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Sarah Brockman Attended NeurIPS 2019</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/travel-sarah/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Sarah Brockman Attended NeurIPS 2019" /><published>2019-12-19T19:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2019-12-19T19:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/travel-sarah</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/travel-sarah/">&lt;p&gt;This December, I was given the opportunity to attend NeurIPS 2019 in Vancouver, Canada. Not
only did I have the chance to attend a wide range of talks by machine learning experts in
industry and academia, I had the privilege of presenting the paper I co-authored at one of the
poster sessions. This was my first-ever experience presenting at a poster session, and I loved
every second. It was great to speak with other researchers about my work and get feedback in
person, as well as listen and respond to interesting questions about the paper I had not
previously considered.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Throughout the conference, I had several exciting conversations with fellow researchers about
their work as well as my own. I was introduced to so much research I had no idea was going on
(including some stuff I’ve briefly thought about before and wondered if anyone was working on
it!) I discovered numerous papers that I look forward to reading after speaking to their authors.
Overall, it was great to spend the week with machine learning researchers from all over the
world who are very passionate and driven about their work. It was very inspiring and the
conference left me with a new excitement toward my work. Thank you for the opportunity CS
Women!!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>linglonglinglong</name></author><summary type="html">This December, I was given the opportunity to attend NeurIPS 2019 in Vancouver, Canada. Not only did I have the chance to attend a wide range of talks by machine learning experts in industry and academia, I had the privilege of presenting the paper I co-authored at one of the poster sessions. This was my first-ever experience presenting at a poster session, and I loved every second. It was great to speak with other researchers about my work and get feedback in person, as well as listen and respond to interesting questions about the paper I had not previously considered.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/blog/travel-sarah.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Sandhya Saisubramanian in IROS 2019 in Macau, China</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/travel-sandhya/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Sandhya Saisubramanian in IROS 2019 in Macau, China" /><published>2019-11-07T19:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2019-11-07T19:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/travel-sandhya</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/travel-sandhya/">&lt;p&gt;In November 2019, I had the opportunity to present my work and attend the Intelligent Robots and Systems (IROS) conference at Macau, China. The conference is a great opportunity to meet researchers from various sub-fields of AI and robotics. Thanks to the support of CS Women travel grant, I was able to travel to Macau to present my paper.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The conference was a 5-day event and the attendees were a mix of students, professors, and researchers from the industry. It turned out to be a wonderful experience for me to meet my research community from around the world and share ideas. I was also able to attend several talks and workshop sessions that were part of the conference. It was interesting to hear from many different perspectives and I was able to learn a lot from the speakers at the sessions of workshop and the conference, and from conversations with
the other attendees.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall, the event was enjoyable and beneficial to me. I am thankful to CSWomen group for providing their generous financial support. It helped cover some of the travel expenses to attend this wonderful event!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sandhya Saisubramanian&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>linglonglinglong</name></author><summary type="html">In November 2019, I had the opportunity to present my work and attend the Intelligent Robots and Systems (IROS) conference at Macau, China. The conference is a great opportunity to meet researchers from various sub-fields of AI and robotics. Thanks to the support of CS Women travel grant, I was able to travel to Macau to present my paper.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Soha Rostaminia attends ACM Symposium on Eye Tracking Research and Applications</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/travel-rostaminia/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Soha Rostaminia attends ACM Symposium on Eye Tracking Research and Applications" /><published>2019-07-06T20:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2019-07-06T20:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/travel-rostaminia</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/travel-rostaminia/">&lt;p&gt;In the last week of June 2019, I had the opportunity to present two of my projects, titled “iLid: eyewear solution for low-power fatigue and drowsiness monitoring” and “W!NCE: eyewear solution for upper face action units monitoring”, at the ACM symposium on Eye Tracking Research and Applications (ETRA) in Denver, Colorado. During the poster fast forward session, I gave a small introductory talk for each of the projects and then during the poster session, I introduced my proposed work in details and showed demo videos. This gave me the opportunity to discuss my projects with many people and got a lot of valuable feedback.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/blog/travel-rostaminia-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;A Shot of The Conference&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The interesting part of this conference was the diverse attendees and companies who gathered from all around the world: Germany, Sweden, Switzerland, Finland, Austria, UK, Canada, States, Japan, China, and etc. The environment of the conference was also very dynamic and energetic as each of these popular eye tracking companies had their own stations, and attendees could freely test their newest devices and talk with them about state-of-the-art products. This vibrant connection between academia and industry was really unique, fun to participate, and educative.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am really grateful to the CSWomen group for providing the financial support. It helped me cover some of the expenses to participate in this great event.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>linglonglinglong</name></author><summary type="html">In the last week of June 2019, I had the opportunity to present two of my projects, titled “iLid: eyewear solution for low-power fatigue and drowsiness monitoring” and “W!NCE: eyewear solution for upper face action units monitoring”, at the ACM symposium on Eye Tracking Research and Applications (ETRA) in Denver, Colorado. During the poster fast forward session, I gave a small introductory talk for each of the projects and then during the poster session, I introduced my proposed work in details and showed demo videos. This gave me the opportunity to discuss my projects with many people and got a lot of valuable feedback.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/blog/travel-rostaminia-1.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Mikayla Timm attends CVPR 2019 in Long Beach, CA</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/travel-timm/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Mikayla Timm attends CVPR 2019 in Long Beach, CA" /><published>2019-06-17T20:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2019-06-17T20:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/travel-timm</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/travel-timm/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Giving a spotlight talk and poster presentation of my research at the &lt;a href=&quot;http://cvpr2019.thecvf.com/&quot;&gt;IEEE Conference on Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition (CVPR 2019)&lt;/a&gt; this summer has given me valuable experience in presenting and communicating my work with others in the community.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/blog/travel-timm-2.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Timm - FGVC6 Spotlight&quot; style=&quot;margin: 15px 10px 10px 0; height=600px; width=600px&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Thanks to CS Women and Women for UMass, I was able to attend CVPR 2019, a top-tier computer vision conference, located in Long Beach, California! I had the privilege of presenting my research at the conference in the &lt;a href=&quot;https://sites.google.com/view/fgvc6/home&quot;&gt;6th Fine-grained Visual Categorization workshop&lt;/a&gt;. Introducing my research in a spotlight talk in front of hundreds of people was an empowering experience, and a great opportunity for me to practice my public speaking skills.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/blog/travel-timm-3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Convention Center&quot; style=&quot;margin: 15px 10px 10px 0; height=600px; width=600px&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many people attended the conference from academia and industry alike, all congregating together with the common goal of furthering the advancement of computer vision. I had the chance to network with many professors and fellow graduate students whose research I’ve been following. I also got the chance to talk with industry professionals about how their companies use computer vision and machine learning to improve user experiences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/blog/travel-timm-4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Long Beach Convention Center&quot; style=&quot;margin: 15px 10px 10px 0; height=600px; width=600px&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve greatly enjoyed this opportunity to learn more about my area of research, share my work with others, and network with the computer vision community this summer in Long Beach!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A huge thank you to &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.umass.edu/wfum/&quot;&gt;Women for UMass Amherst&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://cswomenumass.github.io/index.html&quot;&gt;CS Women&lt;/a&gt; for supporting my research aspirations by helping fund my trip to CVPR!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/blog/travel-timm-5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Long Beach&quot; style=&quot;margin: 15px 10px 10px 0; height=600px; width=600px&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>linglonglinglong</name></author><summary type="html">Giving a spotlight talk and poster presentation of my research at the IEEE Conference on Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition (CVPR 2019) this summer has given me valuable experience in presenting and communicating my work with others in the community.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/blog/travel-timm-1.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Emily Herbert attended Programming Languages Implementation Summer School (PLISS)</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/travel-herbert/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Emily Herbert attended Programming Languages Implementation Summer School (PLISS)" /><published>2019-06-12T20:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2019-06-12T20:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/travel-herbert</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/travel-herbert/">&lt;p&gt;Earlier this summer I had the opportunity to attend the &lt;a href=&quot;https://pliss2019.github.io/&quot;&gt;Programming Languages Implementation Summer School (PLISS)&lt;/a&gt;, a week long summer school program for early-career programming languages researchers held in Bertinoro, Italy. The summer school focused on preparing students for PL research by introducing and teaching core PL concepts, discussing possible future research areas, and connecting attendees with both new and experienced colleagues in their field.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Each day consisted of four lectures, with topics ranging from a review of the implications of &lt;a href=&quot;https://pliss2019.github.io/ben_titzer_spectre_slides.pdf&quot;&gt;Spectre&lt;/a&gt; to an introduction to &lt;a href=&quot;http://plasma-umass.org/pliss2019/&quot;&gt;first-class continuations&lt;/a&gt; and many of the topics being completely new to me. Students were encouraged to actively participate and ask questions, and several of the lectures turned into interactive sessions with the speaker. This was one of the things that I really appreciated about PLISS - the atmosphere felt very welcoming and it was clear that the speakers’ goal was student comprehension. PLISS fostered a great learning environment, and I left with more questions than I arrived with!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/blog/travel-herbert-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;A Picture from a Italy Church&quot; style=&quot;-webkit-transform: rotate(90deg);
    -moz-transform: rotate(90deg);
    -ms-transform: rotate(90deg);
    -o-transform: rotate(90deg);
    transform: rotate(90deg);
    margin-top: 100px;
    margin-bottom: 100px;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition to the lectures, another focus of the summer school was connecting the students with others in their field, and PLISS offered us many opportunities to socialize and talk science. It was fun to hear about what projects the other students were working on and I got some good feedback about my own project. Moreover, it was reassuring to meet researchers in the same stage of their careers that I am in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Much thanks to the CS Women’s group for their support in subsidizing my trip! I highly recommend PLISS, or another summer school in your field, I had an awesome time!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/blog/travel-herbert-3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;A Picture of Italy&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;P.S. Thanks to Hanneli Tavante, another attendee for the group photo&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>linglonglinglong</name></author><summary type="html">Earlier this summer I had the opportunity to attend the Programming Languages Implementation Summer School (PLISS), a week long summer school program for early-career programming languages researchers held in Bertinoro, Italy. The summer school focused on preparing students for PL research by introducing and teaching core PL concepts, discussing possible future research areas, and connecting attendees with both new and experienced colleagues in their field.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/blog/travel-herbert-1.gif" /></entry></feed>